After dropping any incomplete data,
删除不完整的数据
and taking a look at the results,
并查看了结果后
you are test with normalizing the data.
下面你的任务是归一化数据
Above, when we looked at our clean counties DataFrame,
在上面查看了 clean_counties_df 后
you can see that the range of features was really large.
可以看到 特征范围很大
Some of these columns have really big and wide ranging values,
某些列的值很大 范围很宽
and others have percentage values.
其他列具有百分比值
Since unsupervised learning relies on looking at the relationships between features,
因为非监督式学习需要查看特征之间的关系
I want these features to be consistently comparable.
所以我要将这些特征变得可比较
In fact, I want to scale all of
实际上 我要将
these numerical features into a range between zero and one,
所有这些数值特征的范围变成 0-1
and I can start to do this with a call to the sklearn.preprocessing library,
首先调用 sklearn.preprocessing 库
where I can import a MinMaxScaler.
导入 MinMaxScaler
I can create a scalar object,
我可以创建一个 scalar 对象
which is able to look at the minimum and maximum values in a feature range,
它能够查看特征范围内的最小值和最大值
and divide every value by that range to get a normalized value between zero and one.
并使每个值除以该范围 获得 0-1 之间的标准化值
So I'm creating a scalar,
我创建了一个 scalar
then to get my county scale DataFrame,
然后 为了获得 counties_scaled DataFrame
I'm using fit_transform, passing in my clean counties DataFrame as a float type,
我将调用 fit_transform 传入浮点型 clean_counties_df
and applying that MinMaxScaler.
并应用 MinMaxScaler
This is a pretty typical normalization step.
这是一个很常见的归一化步骤
Now you want the features and the indices to be the same for this scale DataFrame,
scaled DataFrame 的特征和索引
as they are in our clean counties DataFrame,
要与 clean_counties_df 的一样
that is I want the columns to be our features,
我们希望列为特征
and the indices to be our state county indices.
索引为 State-County 索引
Let's see the result, now I can see the all of
看看结果 可以看到
these numerical values are in decimal ranges.
所有这些数值都位于小数范围内
I can even go one step further and check that the maximum and minimum are what I expect.
还可以进一步检查最大值和最小值是否符合预期
By calling.describe on a DataFrame,
通过对 DataFrame 调用 .describe
I can see steps like the minimum and the maximum value,
可以看到最小值和最大值等统计量
and indeed, they're zero and one respectively for all of our numerical columns.
的确所有数值列的最小值和最大值都分别是0 和 1
So we cleaned our data,
我们清理了数据
we got rid of our categorical columns,
删除了类别列
and now we've just scaled it.
并且缩放了范围
Now we're almost ready to put this through a PCA model,
下面差不多可以将输入传入 PCA 模型
and reduce the dimensionality of this data for future analysis.
并降维以供后续分析使用
Let's learn more about PCA next.
下面我们将详细了解 PCA